<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SNAKE GO</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">SNAKE GO</string>
    <string name="dia_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="dia_score">Score: </string>
    <string name="dia_ok">Resume</string>
    <string name="dia_cncl">Cancel</string>
    <string name="highscore">High Score</string>
    <string name="rturn">Return</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="score">Score:</string>
    <string name="h_scores">High Scores</string>
    <string name="resume">Resume Game</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit Game</string>
    <string name="type_your_username">Type your Username</string>
    <string-array name="milestones">
        <item>Just a walk in the park</item>
        <item>You\'re a beast.</item>
        <item>You rock!</item>
        <item>You\'re still playing this game?</item>
        <item>You\'re a SnakeGo god</item>
        <item>You\'re a living legend</item>
        <item>You\'re SnakeGo accomplishments will be recorded in the annals of history</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="snakego_poetry">Snake Poetry for our fellow SnakeGoers&#8230;\n\nThe appearance of
        a snake can evoke intense feelings of terror. And rightly
        so considering a snakebite can be so deadly. But beyond this visceral response,
        the snake is a multifaceted symbol. A little investigating reveals rich histories of the
        snake showing up in literature, art, and mythologies from around the world. Some of the
        following descriptions are among the most prevalent meanings attributed to the snake,
        despite cultural inflections: \n\nrenewal, as snakes periodically shed their skin,
        spiritual and physical rebirth,
        resurrection, life, Mother Earth, pregnancy, primordial nature, the sea, good and evil,
        the sun and moon, power, knowledge, cunning, deceit, and death. Snakes are sometimes
        portrayed as guardians of treasure, esoteric knowledge, and the afterlife. They also
        connote venom, medicine, expanded consciousness, the elixir of life, and immortality.\n\nIn
        Greek mythology, Asclepius is a god of healing and medicine who carries a snake
        entwined staff. The rod of Asclepius as its often called can be found throughout the world
        on flags and emblems of distinguished medical institutions, such as the World Health
        Organization and the American Medical Association.  The rod of Asclepius is sometimes confused
        with the Caduceus, a rod with wings and two snakes wrapped around it, carried by the Greek god
        Hermes. Although their meanings overlap, when two snakes are coiled around each other
        (or a staff in this case), this tends to signify the union of opposing forces, similar
        to the yin and the yang. \n\nSimilarly, the Ouroboros is a well-known example of snake
        iconography which depicts a snake eating its tail. This represents cyclic manifestation,
        re-absorption, wholeness, Earth, and the infinite.\n\nThe snake is
        widely considered to be synonymous with the serpent. In some East Asian cultures, there\'s no
        distinction between snakes, serpents, and dragons. \n\nWith so many meanings attached to the
        snake, it\'s a difficult creature to pin down, figuratively. How does the snake fit into
        our lives? Why do we impart such significance to the snake? We see its frequent recurrence -
        in art, movies, and literature? \n\nOne element of the snake\'s appeal is arguably its
        difficulty in being pinned down. The mysticism that surrounds the snake comes at least in part
        from its skin shedding trait. The snake\'s impression of continual regeneration combined with the terror, awe, and
        mystery of its lethal venom is a paradox that parallels life. Deep questions remain
        about the meaning of life. These are often wrapped in metaphors, symbols, and contradictions.
        As a wise person once said, \"to live is to suffer&#8230; to survive is to find some meaning in the
        suffering.\" Ascribing some meaning to the snake is one way we have survived. Many of life\'s paradoxes
        lie outside our ability to understand. They are better left as symbols that refer to that which
        we don\'t understand. This can offer us some humility and peace. In one manifestation of snake
        iconography, the Ouroboros, life eats life, creating death&#8230; changing, evolving,
        self-generating&#8230; this captures a lasting conundrum that radiates out (and in) -
        beyond to infinity, residing in a timeless place, and constituting an unnameable transcendence.
        As such, the snake stays. \n\nSnakeGo\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n
        \n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nSources \n\nWikipedia \n\nAn Illustrated Encyclopedia of
        Traditional Symbols by J.C. Cooper \n\nThe Power of Myth by Joseph Campbell
        \n\nDictionary.com </string>
</resources>
